

REAJ MORSHED REJA

Ho:2/1, R: 4, Block: F Mirpur-2. **↑**

(+880)1630630899

rejakazi02@gmail.com ✓

Reaj Morshed (Reja) in

My website: **rejakazi.com** /



OBJECTIVE

A motivated, passionate, responsible, strategic and enterprising young professional whose aim is to establish himself as a well renowned creative person through developing his knowledge by working in a well reputed organization, gather experiences of working in a team and gain the capability of leading team which will increase his confident and working skills and betterment for his future.



EDUCATION

B.Sc. Engg. in CSE | Bangladesh University of Business & Technology (BUBT)

2017 - 2021

CGPA 3.13 out of 4.00

HSC | DK. Ideal Syed Atahar Ali

2013 - 2015

GPA 4.58 out of 5.00

Activities and Societies: Sport Club, Debate Club

SSC | Mandra Radhagonj United Institution

2011 - 2013

GPA 4.25 out of 5.00

Activities and Societies: Sport Club, Debate Club



EXPERIENCE

Data Annotator | ROYEL IT LTD.

SEP 2019 - FEB 2021

Professional Data Annotator

Lecturer | IQRA ACADEMIC & COACHING

MAR 2018 - FEB 2020

Lecturer of Mathematics & ICT

Volunteer | BACKDOOR PRIVATE LIMITED

SEP 2020 - NOV 2020

Worked on various events



- **Programming Languages:** C, C++, C#.
- Frontend Languages: HTML, CSS, Dot Net, ASP .Net (MVC).
- **Database Languages:** MySQL.

- Networking Tools: Cisco Packet Tracer
- **Designing / Editing Tools:** Adobe Photoshop, Wondershare Fillmora
- **Interpersonal Skills:** Public Speaking, Team Leadership, Teaching, Training.

PROJECTS

- <u>Launch management system</u>
 Desktop application based on Visual Studio with C# and MySQL.
- Apartment rent management system
 Web application based on Visual Studio with MVC dot net and MySQL.
- Android Apartment Payment Application
 An android application various features of rent payment based on Android studio.

LANGUAGE PROFICINECY

• Bangla & English
Full Professional Proficiency



EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Gamer
- Football Player
- Cricket Player
- Swimmer
- Social Worker
- Traveler

REFERENCES

Dr.Muhammad Frioz Mridha

Assistant Professor & chairman
Department of Computer Science & Engineering
Bangladesh University of Business and Technology.

Email: firoz@bubt.edu.bd

Md.Saifur Rahman

Assistant Professor
Department of Computer Science & Engineering
Bangladesh University of Business and Technology.

Email: saifurs@gmail.com

Signature

Reaj Morshed Reja